

FCO. JOEL MORANDO

PORTFOLIO

pacomorando.github.io/portfolio

CONTACT

TEL +52 1 33-13-52-76-19
ADR Col. Independencia
Guadalajara Jal. Mex.

EMAIL

paco.morando@gmail.com

.

EDUCATION

I'm graduated as a Civil Architect at **University of Guadalajara** since 2014.

SKILLS

- Android development (front/back)
- Web development (front/back)
- Graphic and UX-UI design.
- Project managment
- Architecture design
- Bilingual SP/EN

I also have knowledge in software architecture, object-oriented design, development methodologies such as RUP, and some agile methods, UML, OOP, and design patterns.

TECHNOLOGIES I KNOW

SpringBoot Angular AndroidStudio Java TypeScript MySQL SQLite Git/Github HTML XML.

SOFTWARE I KNOW

Photoshop, Inkscape, Illustrator, Office, 3DMax, SketchUp, AutoCAD, VRay, Indesign.

PROFILE

Self-taught, with 3 years and a half of experience in learning and developing both frontend and backend for mobile and web applications.

I have 14 years of experience working with large teams and leading some small teams in various fields related to my professional degree.

I am open to learning new things. Being open-minded has been a crucial part of my personal and professional development. I have a receptive and inclusive attitude in discuss and generate ideas. I always prioritize objectivity and analysis over negativity and prejudice.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Open to work - Feelance | 2023 - ACTU

Alongside to my continually learning about programming and software design I'm still taking commissions for consulting, and design of various kind of projects.

Udip | 2022 - 2023 Project manager

I managed, designed, and developed urbanization projects with a small team of architects.

I conducted 3D modeling, created renderings, prepared Photoshop presentations, and generated construction drawings, among other tasks.

Iprodisa | 2019 - 2022

Project manager

My role, in addition to being a CAD draftsman and co-designer, included managing a small design team and a group of workers in both large and small projects for mechanical, electro-mechanical, and industrial projects. I worked for various companies, such as Boehringer, Bemis, Interlub, Bio Zoo, among others.

Feelance | 2017 - 2019

I made commissions for architectural projects, graphic design and mechanical engineering blueprints.

Saturn Apple Studios | 2016 - 2017

Design manager

My rol was the designer and quality supervisor, here i had the opportunity ti aquire experience with UI an UX design.

I also made basic programming in C#, and graphic design.

Saturn apple studios was a startup focused in game, web and movil development.

Desing Assitant | 2009 - 2016

I worked as a CAD draftsman, construction supervisor, and design assistant in a few of architecture and engineering companies while I was in college.